[
  {
    "question": "Can you access Cookie using javascript?",
    "a": "true",
    "b": "false",
    "c": "-",
    "d": "-",
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "Yes! JavaScript can also manipulate cookies using the cookie property of the Document object."
  },
  {
    "question": "How can you get the type of arguments passed to a function?",
    "a": "using typeof operator",
    "b": "using getType function",
    "c": "both of the above",
    "d": "none of the above",
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "Using typeof operator, we can get the type of arguments passed to a function."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which built-in method calls a function for each element in the array?",
    "a": "while()",
    "b": "loop()",
    "c": "forEach()",
    "d": "None of the above",
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "forEach() method calls a function for each element in the array."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which built-in method returns the string representation of the number's value?",
    "a": "toValue()",
    "b": "toNumber()",
    "c": "toString()",
    "d": "None of the above",
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "toString() method returns the string representation of the number's value."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of Number object returns the number's value?",
    "a": "toString()",
    "b": "valueOf()",
    "c": "toLocaleString()",
    "d": "toPrecision()",
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "valueOf() − Returns the number's value."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string?",
    "a": "slice()",
    "b": "split()",
    "c": "substr()",
    "d": "substring()",
    "correct": "d",
    "explanation": "substring() − Returns the characters in a string between two indexes into the string."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of String object returns the primitive value of the specified object.",
    "a": "toLocaleUpperCase()",
    "b": "toUpperCase()",
    "c": "toString()",
    "d": "valueOf()",
    "correct": "d",
    "explanation": "valueOf() − Returns the primitive value of the specified object."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of String object causes a string to be displayed as a superscript, as if it were in a <sup> tag?",
    "a": "sup()",
    "b": "small()",
    "c": "strike()",
    "d": "sub()",
    "correct": "a",
    "explanation": "sup() − Causes a string to be displayed as a superscript, as if it were in a <sup> tag."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of Array object applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value?",
    "a": "pop()",
    "b": "push()",
    "c": "reduce()",
    "d": "reduceRight()",
    "correct": "c",
    "explanation": "reduce() − Applies a function simultaneously against two values of the array (from left-to-right) as to reduce it to a single value."
  },
  {
    "question": "Which of the following function of Array object removes the first element from an array and returns that element?",
    "a": "reverse()",
    "b": "shift()",
    "c": "slice()",
    "d": "some()",
    "correct": "b",
    "explanation": "shift() − Removes the first element from an array and returns that element."
  }
]
